<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- This file contains pSensorViewer documentation -->
<?xml-stylesheet href="../../../doc/xmldocumentation.css" type="text/css"?> 
<xmldoc>
  <moosapp>

     <info>
        <name>pTrustGPS</name>
        <organization>Toutatis AUVs - ENSTA Bretagne</organization>
        <date>2015</date>
        <authors>
           <author>Jeremy NICOLA</author>
        </authors>
        <licence>MIT</licence>
     </info>

     <documentation>
        <synopsis>
          This process publishes a single variable that says if we should trust GPS measurements or not.
            If either:
            - we send a command for the AUV to dive below a given thresold, at which we are sure the GPS sensor is submerged
            - we measure a depth at which we are sure the GPS sensor is submerged
            - the QUALITY signal of the GPS is false
            we should not use the GPS.
            When the AUV dives for some time and surface to get a GPS fix, the Kalman filter inside the GPS sensor might not converge instantly, therefore we should wait a bit before trusting its position.
            Therefore, we check the latest PARANOIA_LEVEL number of GPS measurements. If ALL of them were considered trustable, we trust the current GPS measurements. That means that if a single GPS measurement was not considered reliable in this buffer, we don't believe the GPS for the moment.
        </synopsis>
        <interface>
           <subscriptions>
              <moosvar>
                 <varname>DESIRED_DEPTH</varname>
                 <vartype>double</vartype>
                 <varinfo>Desired depth command sent to the AUV. It is positive towards the center of earth, and we convert it internally into an altitude, in meters.</varinfo>
              </moosvar>

              <moosvar>
                 <varname>KELLER_DEPTH</varname>
                 <vartype>double</vartype>
                 <varinfo>Current depth of the AUV, measured with the Keller pressure sensor. It is positive towards the center of earth, and we convert it internally into an altitude, in meters.</varinfo>
              </moosvar>

              <moosvar>
                 <varname>GPS_QUALITY</varname>
                 <vartype>bool</vartype>
                 <varinfo>GPS Quality estimation, given directly by the GPS sensor. False means we shouldn't believe the sensor, tue means we might believe it.</varinfo>
              </moosvar>
           </subscriptions>
           <publications>
              <moosvar>
                 <varname>GPS_TRUST</varname>
                 <vartype>bool</vartype>
                 <varinfo>True means we can believe the current GPS measurements, false means we shouldn't.</varinfo>
              </moosvar>
           </publications>
        </interface>

        <optional-comments>
           No comment.
        </optional-comments>

        <suggested-improvements>
           No suggested improvements.
        </suggested-improvements>
     </documentation>

  </moosapp>
</xmldoc>
