<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- This file contains iLidarMove documentation -->
<?xml-stylesheet href="../../../../doc/xmldocumentation.css" type="text/css"?>
<xmldoc>
  <moosapp>

     <info>
        <name>iLidarMove</name>
        <organization>Demopol - ENSTA Bretagne</organization>
        <date>2015</date>
        <authors>
           <author>Elouan Autret student Ensta Bretagne</author>
        </authors>
        <licence>MIT</licence>
     </info>

     <documentation>
        <synopsis>
          This app can connect to RX-28 Dynamixel Servo Motor and a LidarLiteV2 (PulseLight) via 
an Arduino board with a serial port.

          The app use the  API furnish by Dynamixel and PulseLigth to scan the aera in front of the Lidar mounted on the servo.An Iteration give us a bearing and a distance for an obstacle.

          Angle_min = [0,1023] minimum angle  of rotation for the servo
          Angle_max = [0,1023] maximum angle of rotation for the servo
          If the lidar look front the angle is 0° and correspond to 512. 0 is -150 and 1023 is 150. Max should be higher than min. The servo will rotationate between those two values. 
          
          Index_servo number for the url of the serial port of servo as in /dev/ttyUSBX
          URL_LIDAR  URl of the serial port with the arduino connected to the lidar
          Servo_Id = [1-255] as you can put more than one RX-28 servo motor linked you need an id to give order to the servo can be change by managing the servo via the Windows program from Dynamixel
          Servo_speed = [0-1023] set the speed of the rotation of the servo from 0 rpm to around 117 rpm (depend also of the load on the servo);  
        </synopsis>
        <interface>
           <publications>
              <moosvar>
                 <varname>LIDAR_DISTANCE</varname>
                 <vartype>int</vartype>
                 <varinfo>distance of the detected object</varinfo>
              </moosvar>
              <moosvar>
                 <varname>LIDAR_ANGLE</varname>
                 <vartype>double</vartype>
                 <varinfo>bearing (relative to servo) of the object</varinfo>
              </moosvar>
           </publications>
        </interface>
        <!-- if there is a bug or a special fact to know.. -->
        <optional-comments>
           Other parameters are available but not fully implemented.
        </optional-comments>
        <!-- if something can be improved -->
        <suggested-improvements>
           Joint the ANGLE and DISTANCE to assure synchronization upon reading of those DATA.
           Change Dynamixel library to put URL instead of number in order to indicate serial port of the servo motor. 
        </suggested-improvements>
     </documentation>

  </moosapp>
</xmldoc>
